I wonder where it flew from, but it was blooming well under the guardrail.
So, you can find them in asphalt-like places like this.
If there is even a small space between the seeds
Beautiful flower!
Tatsunamisoma, or something like that.
So cute!
Amazing.
It blooms even though there is no soil?
Beautiful!
I like the purple color, don't you?
It's so cute!
Plants are amazing. And the next thing I think about... is... a classmate of mine... who used to live nearby.
I had a classmate or something, I don't know... in kindergarten, maybe... and his parents lived in the neighborhood with him until he was old enough to go to elementary school.
He lived in the neighborhood until he was old enough to go to elementary school.
He knows a lot about plants.
But he's there, isn't he?
Yes, yes.
Isn't it cool that he knows so much about plants?
He's cool.
He's got his picture book open.
I told him... I didn't tell him...
I admire him.
I wasn't really into trains or anything.
I was interested in plants, but I could remember the names of all the plants.
Wow.
I was influenced.
I'd tell girls, "Hey, this one looks like that one.
Oh, I'm gonna be popular with the girls.
You were a little popular with the girls.
So it really worked.
I was popular.
I was in the first or second grade of elementary school.
Wow.
Sure. I don't know what to say... about trains, for example.
Don't all boys like that kind of thing? I do, and being knowledgeable about them can be a little sarcastic.
Well, well, well... I'm glad you're trying so hard to remember, and I know you're proud of it.
I know you're proud of it, but I don't feel bad when you say you know a lot about plants, like this.
I'm sure you're right, it's amazing... the plant effect is amazing.
I think it's a little different when it comes to animals... animals are a little too maniacal
I'm not sure why plants want to make people feel so bad.
I don't know why... they give off carbon dioxide oxygen, right?
That's the feeling of gratitude we humans have had since we were born.
Thank you for everything. It's in our genes. I see.
It's in our DNA.
But maybe you have a point.
No, I'm serious.
I'm sure only the regulars are coming in now.
We'll try to get more customers to come, too.
We'd be very grateful if you could come. I'd be very grateful.
So, if you have any more letters, we'll be waiting for them here.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
It looks painful.
Are you okay?
The live broadcast has begun.
Has it begun?
Hello.
I'm Subie.
I'm an idiot.
I'm, uh...
Dumbass.
I'm an idiot.
I'm a moron
Triple crown, triple crown, triple crown...
I'm the Triple Crown Winner.
Yes, I know...
I'll go on and show you the roll-nanna.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, I'm working on something.
I'm not trying very hard, you know.
Roll nana, too.
Roll nana sounds kind of delicious.
Like a roll cake.
Rolls, 7 kilos.
Roll nana, I'll show you.
Is that okay?
Yes, please.
Cue.
Cue... it's an industry term or a TV term.
It's also used in movies.
It's like when you say, "Cue me, please.
Like a cue.
Cue.
What does that mean?
Is it an abbreviation? CUE.
What is it? What is it in Japanese?
But I'm sure it means something.
I'll be waiting for you.
Yes, yes, yes... it was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
I don't know... it's a coffee shop, you have to have customers.
That's right.
It's a problem, but like this, I'm an idiot.
Idiot.
I'm an idiot.
It's fun to be like that.
That's right.
The customers who come from the outside, they tell us things we don't know.
Yes, it was a lot of fun.
And then, what a surprise... a picture of the Servon brothers!
I'm not here either...
I've never been to Kyoto before in my life... and I've never been to Kyoto before in my life...
Well, I've been to Kyoto before via...
I've been to Kyoto before, but this is the first time I've been to Kyoto for sightseeing.
I'm glad I did it!
It's the best part of a school trip
It's great to go there, but now that I'm older, I can see how amazing it is.
It's really amazing, is this really the stage of Kiyomizu?
Anyway, it's the center of Kyoto's temple area because it has a long history as the center of the Warring States period.
It's like Shibuya's Center Street.
The architecture of Japan is the pinnacle of Japanese architecture.
It's a lot taller than you think they built it back then.
It's like a pyramid.
And we're good together.
Kyoto is the most beautiful place in Japan... and Kyoto is for shows.
Oh, my God!
I'm so glad you got the landing right now...
thank you!
I'll be here for about 10 or 15 minutes.
And a little bit on the surface, yes...
When you see the Golden Pavilion in person, it's a little bit different from the picture.
I was surprised when I went there.
I'm sure Subhi and I would have had the same reaction if we'd gone there.
I'm sure you're wondering if I'm a naki-nin, but I can do it if I see it.
I'm not sure why I made it gold.
The person who created the Muromachi bug, who had the money, had the power and the power of power at that time.
The person who concentrated the power of power on him at that time was playing with him like a symbol.
The ticket is a bill.
That's why it's so cool.
So it's really cool.
It's very Kyoto-like.
I love it!
It's Kyoto, so how can I say it?
There are so many more temples and shrines
There are so many temples and shrines
It's really...
We stayed here for two days and one night.
It's not enough.
Not even close.
More than one night was not enough.
And Kyoto is a really long place.
Even in the daytime.
Kyoto was the capital of Japan for a long time, right?
In a very real sense, Tokyo is a very historical place, even if I say why Tokyo did it, it's only recently.
So people in Kyoto are really nice and elegant!
Boo boo, I'm going to aim for that too!
I want to learn from them.
I'd like to learn from them.
I've heard that the number of foreigners has been increasing.
I went there in January, but today I'm going to see a strawbale rice cake inside the Cube Temple.
I went there in January, but today I went to a store inside the Cube Temple, where they serve warabimochi (rice cakes) and other such delicacies.
Wow, the food at the swimming pool is amazing!
I'm sure it's the same everywhere you go!
Kyoto is also a long time since it was the center of Japan's culinary culture, so yes, it's true.
The food is always good, no matter what you eat, and the seafood is delicious too.
But Kyoto people drive like that.
I bought some souvenirs, but I left them backstage.
I'm buying some souvenirs, but I left them in the dressing room.
I gave him a souvenir from Mie Prefecture and he ate it with me for the rest of his life.
The dome is still a little scary.
Ise Udon and Ise Udon are the same thing
You know, there's the Ise Jingu shrine, right?
It's udon that's eaten locally and it's not in a soup or anything.
It's good.
I'm glad you like it.
Take a look.
Look at this. I'm like this, and you're like that.
Cotton candy...
So it's not so bad, is it?
It's got a great strawberry flavor!
Master, you're on the same level as the rest of the museum!
Isn't it on the level?
Speaking of level, I saw this... the devil's beer!
I thought this might be it... what was it?
I bought a packet of this beer!
A red-colored beer with a pop of dolophilic aroma and a strong bitterness.
It's a red beer with Pop's dolophilic aroma and a strong bitterness.
I'd like to see something a little red.
I see people are starting to open beer with white recordings.
I've always imagined cotton candy in this way.
I'm sure it's fine if I open that one time.
Please open it once...
I see.
after Days
I see...
A whole bunch of them... a little pink strawberry...
A whole bunch of these... with a little pink strawberry inside.
You can just eat them...
I'll just have a bite.
Please, go ahead.
Sweet, sweet, sweet.
It tastes like strawberries with a hint of sour.
So it's a real strawberry?
It's even more strawberry than I expected.
It's so good!
It's so classy.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wait a minute, are you sure they're red?
A little.
It's red.
It's really red.
Wow!
Wow, it's really red!
It's beautiful. Wow, it's beautiful. The reflection is red, too.
This is so stylish! Wow, it's red!
It's so beautiful!
I'll drink it as soon as the camera stops.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Thank you.
I'll wrap it up and drink it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you. It's no big deal.
I'm going to have to go out and get something.
No, no, no. I have to get something too.
Okay, okay, okay...
Let's continue.
Amazing!
Blue Mars... he sent us a great picture too.
I don't know... I haven't seen it recently, but...
But there was a boom of imitation shows.
They used to do imitation shows on prime-time TV.
You know, like a poster or a picture insert.
We used to do our own version of it.
It was amazing!
I'm the only one who looks like Yasen Suruga, while everyone else is dressed in cute outfits.
And Sabo, Yuji Oda's.
By the way, I'm the second in the Mitaka series. The middle school effect.
Joy, the middle school effect... can you sing now?
Now? No, I can't sing now.
Do you remember?
Do you remember? I can't sing.
You were trying to sing.
I'm sure.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I don't remember the effects of high school at all.
I don't remember the effects of high school at all, but I remember elementary school and junior high school very well for some reason.
That's for sure.
I still don't.
Really?
I can go anywhere in the sky and never leave.
The effect during the day was a little different, it was in 3 beats, it wasn't hard, like 1, 41 and 3.
It's not hard, it's like 1, 41, and 3. It's a great melody.
I'm working on it, but I'm looking forward to it.
I'm working on it and I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it!
Mitaka City Daini Junior High School Effect
It's an overage imitation.
me Shiki
I'm looking forward to it!
Shiki, did you see it shine?
Iini-chu Aoge
The sky, the ideal
Aiming for the ideal, I flapped my wings
in the sky for the ideal
kan
So, after this one time, the last
telegraphic transmission
three wings.
God's front tail
Hope is a cloud
like a frame
I'm glad of its name
Mitaka City Daini Junior High School
It's like
If it comes with some kind of guitar, it's usually a good song
A good song
No, this is really good.
Wow!
Even alumni say it's a great school song.
I see.
It's a normal public school.
It's just... it's more like...
It's like "Hope is the Best" or something.
It's more relaxed.
Nice and cool.
And it's all in one place.
It's like a bellows.
And then there's the end of the summary.
It's so stylish.
It's amazing.
And it's amazing that you remember it.
Somehow I just can't forget it.
I knew it sounded beautiful.
Must have rubbed off on you a bit.
Back then.
Yes, yes, yes.
And that's it... Oh, the live broadcast is over.
It's about time.
Then, please watch the live broadcast.
You've read a lot today, right?
Yes, I read a lot today.
Let's do this too.
Hey, for the live audience, I'm sorry to interrupt.
I'm sorry to interrupt your live delivery, but Yuuhi Zadar from Kashiwa City, Chiba Prefecture.
It's been a while since I've sent you a story about insects since spring.
Sorry, Mr. Sarpon.
One fine Sunday afternoon, as I was taking a walk, I looked down at the grass at my feet, and there was an active seven-star ladybug.
I thought it might be okay for Mr. Sarpong, so I got curious and took a picture for my camera.
I'm curious.
It's around here, isn't it? Oh, it's beautiful.
What's with the mouth?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's cute.
Can I have some more pictures?
Mr. Momentoff!
Shizuoka City, Shizuoka Prefecture
The great overmaster
Dear Sarpon
Beautiful byte, Ebiju-chan!
Thank you for your hard work today.
I have been insisting on this since the beginning of the program
I am pleased to make my first post.
I left Kanagawa a few years ago for work
since the mayor was in teaberdiery.
Monday
thank you for all your hard work
I am very thankful that I can now claim everything from "Thank you" to "Thank you very much", so I thought I should express my gratitude in some way and took up my pen.
I wrote the Cat Master because Kayoko Yoshizawa, our guest, mentioned Master as cat-like in her talk about dog people and cat people.
So I wrote "Cat Master". Cat Master!
This is it... hahaha... it's nice and austere, isn't it... and cat too!
Cat Master, please don't be cross with me, Cat Master, you're cute and cuddly, but in this museum, Bill, hey, you can suck my cute paw pads.
It looks like something out of "Listen Up" or something...
Thank you very much.
Cats are everyone's favorite.
I'm sure this will go viral.
Make these masks.
That's right.
Put it on in the morning.
I've had enough of this face.
That's not what I meant.
It's more like, "Why don't we turn him into a cat?
Thank you very much.
That's what I said.
If you have any more letters, please keep sending them to us.
I would appreciate it if you could continue to send them to us.
We are looking forward to hearing from you.
Okay, so...
Let's give credit where credit is due.
Wait a minute, let's put in the credits.
Let's put the credits in.